The earth and the world are two different things. There's the earth, which is where we are
physically from, what we eat from, what feeds us, what is literally our home.
And then there's the world, which is the constructed existence within which we have been
made to exist. So yes, there's the earth and there's the world. The indigenous folks know
what the earth is. We don't know what the earth is anymore because we're all caught up in the
world. And what I'm trying to do is get as many of us as possible before I leave this earth
to understand that if you only know the world, then you don't know the earth. And if you don't
know the earth, then you are simply just a weapon to keep the world going. And the world is killing
the earth. So like my sweater says, grow with the flow. Because what I love most about rivers is you
can't step in the same river twice. Okay. These white men are dangerous. No one is to go near
them.
Streets of Belfast in the dark of early morn.